[
  {
    "url": "best-places-to-retire",
    "cta": {
      "title": "Enable AI-Powered Personalization",
      "subTitle": "Fine-tune content to your needs — remove irrelevant details, add tailored insights",
      "buttonText": "Tailor Content to My Preferences",
      "noThanksText": "No, I rather read the generic article"
    },
    "qna": [
      {
        "questionText": "Do you need access to top-tier healthcare?",
        "answers": [
          { "answerText": "Yes" },
          { "answerText": "No" }
        ]
      },
      {
        "questionText": "Are you okay with cold places which get snow?",
        "answers": [{ "answerText": "Yes" }, { "answerText": "No" }]
      },
      {
        "questionText": "Do statistically high crime rates deter you?",
        "answers": [{ "answerText": "Yes" }, { "answerText": "No" }]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "url": "best-four-wheel-drive-cars",
    "cta": {
      "title": "Enable AI-Powered Personalization",
      "subTitle": "Fine-tune content to your needs — remove irrelevant details, add tailored insights",
      "buttonText": "Tailor Content to My Preferences",
      "noThanksText": "No, I rather read the generic article"
    },
    "qna": [
      {
        "questionText": "What do you plan to use the 4-wheel drive for?",
        "answers": [
          { "answerText": "Commuting" },
          { "answerText": "off-roading" },
          { "answerText": "towing" }
        ]
      },
      {
        "questionText": "Is fuel efficiency important to you?",
        "answers": [{ "answerText": "Yes" }, { "answerText": "No" }]
      },
      {
        "questionText": "How important is the resale value of the vehicle to you?",
        "answers": [
          { "answerText": "Extremely Important" },
          { "answerText": "Medium Importance" },
          { "answerText": "I don't care" }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "url": "lorem-lipsum.html",
    "cta": {
      "title": "Enable AI-Powered Personalization",
      "subTitle": "Fine-tune content to your needs — remove irrelevant details, add tailored insights",
      "buttonText": "Tailor Content to My Preferences",
      "noThanksText": "No, I rather read the generic article"
    },
    "qna": [
      {
        "questionText": "Are you over-weight?",
        "answers": [{ "answerText": "Yes" }, { "answerText": "No" }]
      },
      {
        "questionText": "Do you smoke?",
        "answers": [{ "answerText": "Yes" }, { "answerText": "No" }]
      },
      {
        "questionText": "Do you exercise 2 or more times a week?",
        "answers": [{ "answerText": "Yes" }, { "answerText": "No" }]
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "url": "study.html",
    "cta": {
      "title": "Enable AI-Powered Personalization",
      "subTitle": "Fine-tune content to your needs — remove irrelevant details, add tailored insights",
      "buttonText": "Tailor Content to My Preferences",
      "noThanksText": "No, I rather read the generic article"
    },
    "qna": [
      {
        "questionText": "What level of detail do you want in the article?",
        "answers": [
          { "answerText": "Summarize the main points for a quick read" },
          { "answerText": "Delve into intricate details and nuances" },
          {
            "answerText": "Rearrange the content to match my specific interests"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "questionText": "How often do you wear perfume?",
        "answers": [
          { "answerText": "Every day" },
          { "answerText": "Occasionally" },
          { "answerText": "Rarely" }
        ]
      },
      {
        "questionText": "What type of scent do you prefer?",
        "answers": [
          { "answerText": "Floral" },
          { "answerText": "Sweet" },
          { "answerText": "Spicy" }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]
